vacationoutlet.com 2001-04-05

# Privacy Policy

---  
**For Pricing, Reservations and Additional Questions Call**  
**800-690-2210**  
 Store Locations  
| 

**Vacation Outlet Privacy Policy**  

|   
---  
Vacation Outlet realizes the privacy concerns of today’s internet users. We are committed to protecting your privacy online, and want to give you peace of mind by disclosing all of our intended uses of personal information.   
Whenever personal information (i.e. name, address, credit card numbers, etc.) is desired, or required, we will explicitly ask you to supply it. Any personal information you give us will be used to help us better operate our web site, and to create an e-mailing list for our Alert Me! newsletter. Your name will not be automatically added to this list. You must request that the newsletter be sent to you in order to receive it.   
Vacation Outlet will not disclose any personal information about you or your travel plans to any other persons or companies. Personal information will only be divulged when required by law, or in the interest of protecting the rights and/or property of Vacation Outlet.   
The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide better service to their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Vacation Outlet does use cookies for functional purposes, but does not use them to collect information or for record keeping. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of some web sites if you do so. Setting your computer to refuse cookies will in no way effect Vacation Outlet.   
We hope that this explanation of our privacy policy alleviates any possible concerns. If not, please feel free to e-mail our webmaster with your questions and comments.
